Not as high as air traffic controllers,
but there are far more dentists...
(Raj:)...than air traffic controllers,
so in pure numbers, you're still winning.
(Lalita:)Yay, me.
Do you have a drink
that'll make him less obnoxious?
(Penny:)Drinks do not work that way.
I'd say he's doing fine. Look at her.
The last girl my mom set me up with
had a mustache and a vestigial tail.
- Sorry I'm late.
- What happened?
Nothing. I just really didn't wanna come.
(Sheldon:)Virgin diet Cuba Libre, please.
(Sheldon(on phone):)- Okay.
- In a tall glass with a lime wedge.
(Penny:)Oh, I'll wedge it right in there.
So how's Koothrappali...?
(Sheldon:)Oh, my Lord.
(Raj:)- What?
- That's Princess Panchali.
(Leonard:)I'm pretty sure her name's Lalita.
No, no. Princess Panchali
from The Monkey and The Princess.
(Howard:)Oh, yeah, I tried to watch that online
but they wanted my credit card.